用时... 三十七分钟
And... time! 37 minutes.
这可是我们从家出发
We got from the apartment to
上地铁 再到糕点学校的最快记录了
the subway to the pastry school in record time.
不过得说 我可是没穿胸罩 丁字裤也反穿了
I mean, I'm not wearing a bra and my thong may be on backwards.
丁字裤只要穿得舒服
There's no wrong way to wear a thong,
理它分前及后
as long as it's uncomfortable.
还有 你的胸罩只是装饰而已
And with you, the bra's just for decoration.
我穿着是因为
I have to wear one 'cause you get
你没把孩子放进安全座椅而被发票了
a ticket for not putting the kids in a car seat.
课上见 伙计们 我要和咱家亲耐滴老婆道个别
See you in class, guys. I gotta say good-bye to my wife.
- 你还真以为我会亲你  - 是滴
- Did you think I was gonna kiss you? - Yes!
我是老婆 你是我老公啊
I'm the wife, you're the husband,
你还被我抓到穿着我的衣服
who I caught wearing my clothes one day,
我可是忍气吞声了
but I don't say anything about it...
- 早啊 姑娘们  - 哦 Bebe
- Morning, guys. - Oh, hi, Bebe.
很惊讶看到我 是吧
Surprised to see me, right?
所有人都以为我活不过昨晚了
Everyone always thinks I'm not gonna make it through the night,
不过 姐就在这呢 连我都觉得不可思议
but here I am, even surprised myself.
和随时可能领便当的人
What's it like working in an office
一起工作的滋味如何
with someone who's about to snap like a breadstick?
没你想的般有趣
Not as much fun as you'd think.
不过Bebe人不错的
But Bebe's sweet, and working
而且这工作能供你在糕点学校毕业
here is putting you through pastry school.
- 好的 再见  - 再见
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
- 我要离婚  - 我已提交文件了
- I want a divorce. - I already filed.
== 破产姐妹 第三季 第11集 ==
【H-SGDK】字幕组倾情奉献
== 翻译:理性动物 特特 大姨妈 球球 ==
== 校对&时间轴&封装：天之行者 ==
== 后期：飞在果壳里 统筹：尧之雪 ==
本字幕仅用于交流 学习之用
禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
嘿 老婆 我要五块钱赔我昨天用坏的刮铲
Hey, wife, I need $5 to pay for a spatula I broke yesterday.
我那时候化身Gordon Ramsay模式了
I was having a Gordon Ramsay moment.
我还想和他打了一炮呢
I'd have sex with him, by the way.
怎么 他对你大叫
Why? He'd just be yelling
说你的煮法不对
at you and telling you you're doing it wrong.
是啊 做爱不都如此
Yeah, sex.
拿吧 在我钱包里
Take it. It's in my purse.
嘿 Bebe 你有吃余的药吗
Yo, Bebe, you got any extra pills you're not taking?
不会的 我把药全吃了
No, I'm taking them all.
- 天啊 不会吧  - 什么 我只不过是想买一个 或者两个刮铲
- Oh, my God, no. - What? I just wanted one. Or two.
能给我撸一炮就好 我三点就要参加发泡奶油制作考试了
Just to take the edge off. I have a whipped cream final at 3:00.
不是了 是报纸上的讣告栏 我认识这个人
No. In the obituaries. I know this person.
"Antonia Florentino 享年八十岁 在睡梦中安详离去"
"Antonia Florentino, 80, died peacefully in her sleep."
是自杀的 是吧
That's a suicide, right?
她是我的保姆
She was my nanny.
你还在雇保姆
You still have a nanny?
真走运
Lucky...
她陪我度过了大部分的童年时光
She took care of me most of my childhood.
- 我很爱她  - 节哀
- I loved her so much. - So sorry...
让我想起了我的老邻居Carla
That's kind of how I felt about my old neighbor, Carla.
我是说 她倒没有照顾过我
I mean, she didn't take care of me,
我还是小孩子的时候 她让我用她的水管喝水
but when I was a kid, she used to let me drink out of her hose.
我最后一次见Antonia
The last time I saw Antonia, she was driving me
是她开车戴着邋遢的Nelly Furtado和我去青少年选择奖
and a sloppy Nelly Furtado to the Teen Choice Awards.
哦 上班还让哭了么
Oh, are we allowed to cry at work now?
我可是只敢在车里这么干
'Cause I only do it in my car.
Max 知道我怎么想的么
Max, you know what I just realized?
我的保姆去世后我还是第一次来这里呢
This is the first time I've been here since my nanny died.
你刚才在Chipotle也这么说
You just said that at Chipotle.
十分钟后你又说了一遍 还是在那里
And then you said it again ten minutes later, also at Chipotle.
有点人性好不好 我是为保姆的去世而伤心落泪
Show some sensitivity. I was crying because my nanny died.
而且我们那悼念的早午餐也是在那里吃的
And also because our grief brunch was at Chipotle.
Caroline 你的保姆去世了
Caroline, your nanny passed?
我很同情 宝贝 很遗憾
My sympathies, sweetheart. That's a shame.
不过没什么比一个黑人葬礼爽了
But there is nothing better than a black funeral.
我还正处于84年爷爷葬礼后的宿醉呢
I'm still hung over from my grandpa's in '84.
Earl 我的保姆是个白人
Earl, my nanny was white.
你的保姆是个白人 妹纸你真曾是富人呢
Your nanny was white? Child, you were rich.
看见Han了吗
Have you seen Han?
葬礼明天在费城举行 我要请一天假
The funeral's in Philadelphia tomorrow, and I need the day off.
嗯 我刚才看见他了
Well, I think I saw him earlier,
不过可能是走眼了 那或许是只猫
but then again, it might have been a cat.
嘿 我俩都要请假
Hey, we both need the day off.
我要在精神上支持你
I'm going with you for moral support
而且我要吃人生第一份费城牛肉干酪三明治
my first cheese steak/ I want
我还要像麦粒般骑在独立钟上面爽一下
to ride the liberty bell like a wrecking ball.
这是我在"科技新时代"上 读过有关白矮星 黑洞和天王星
I just read the craziest article in this Popular Science
最扯的文章了
about white dwarfs, black holes, and Uranus.
中坑了 重新再来
Oh, no. Let me start over.
Han 我们明天想请假
Han, we need tomorrow off.
我保姆去世了 她待我如女
My nanny died. She was like a mother to me.
不过她不是你妈妈 餐馆的规定是
But she was not your mother. And diner rules clearly state
你家人去世才能请假
you can only take off for the death of a family member.
是啊 规定也有"工作期间不许饮酒" 可你...
Well, the rules also say "No drinking on the job", but...
好吧 好 你们能去
Okay, yes, you can go.
因为在我们国家里 敬老是很重要的
Because in my culture, it's important to honor the elderly.
我22岁的时候还和一个97岁的老人共享一张双层床呢
I shared a bunk bed with a 97-year-old till I was 22.
你在上面还是下面
Were you on the top or the bottom?
哦 我总是在下面
Oh, I was always the bottom.
又中坑了 重新再来
Oh, no. Let me start over.
嘿 Caroline
Hey, Caroline.
我收到了你保姆去世的短信
I got your nanny death text.
所以我穿黑的以示尊敬
So I'm wearing black out of respect.
还有 我大姨妈来了
And also, I got my period.
- 谢谢 Sopie 你真好人  - 是吗 哪里
- Thanks, Sophie. That's lovely. - It is? Which part?
你看 还在波兰的时候 我的保姆去世了
You know, back in Poland when my nanny died,
我很伤心 我几乎都吃不下她
I was so heartbroken, I could barely eat her.
你把你去世的保姆吃掉了
You ate your dead nanny?
就是只山羊而已 怎称呼也没影响吧
Well, a goat's a goat. It doesn't matter what you name it.
那山羊肉还是很好吃的
It's still good goat meat.
好吧 我去卡位坐着了
All right, I'll be in my booth.
我要点一份金枪鱼三明治 三片Midol止疼片 谢啦
I'm going to order a tuna melt and three Midol, please.
等等 我们怎么去
Wait, how are we gonna get there?
哦 Bebe说她说自己有辆车 我们去找她吧
Oh, Bebe said she had a car, we can just ask her.
我才不要和她坐一辆车
I don't want to get in a car with her.
我都不想和她说话
I don't even want to get in a conversation with her.
我载你们去吧
I can drive you.
不过要去我姐姐那里一趟
We just have to stop at my sister's
她在Bucks县 取一个没有标记的包裹
in Bucks County, pick up an unmarked package,
送到康涅狄格州
and swing by Connecticut to drop it off.
Oleg 你送的东西有什么违禁品么
Oleg, is there anything illegal about this delivery?
没有 就是几双鞋...装了可卡因
No, it's just some shoes... Stuffed with cocaine.
鞋还是大麻做的
Also the shoes are made of hashish.
我还是给Bebe打电话吧
I'll call Bebe.
行 不过我要坐后座
Okay, but I'm sitting in the
要不就会被她传染成神经病了
back 'cause I don't want the crazy to get on me.
Bebe 你能载我们去葬礼 我都不知道该怎么感谢你了
Bebe, I can't thank you enough for driving us to the funeral.
我们才开20英里时速 你可以再开快点的
We're only going 20. You can go faster if you want.
是啊 我们都被树超过去了
Yeah, we just got passed by a tree.
我特别高兴你还带上了
And I'm especially thrilled your nervous cocker spaniel
你那放屁 患了热点病的神经质可卡犬
with gas and hot spots got to join us.
好吧 这下你开到100英里时速了
Okay, now you're going 100.
你可以开慢点的
We can go slower if you want.
不好意思 极端 我的风格
Sorry. Extremes... That's my thing.
有一次 我搬家去东京待了一天
One time I moved to Tokyo for a day.
Max 我又感到了
Max, it just hit me again.
我知道 闻着像是她给狗狗喂了花椰菜
I know. It's like she feeds him broccoli.
Antonia真的去世了
No. That Antonia is really dead.
好消息是 Yelp点评网上说
Well, the good news is, according to Yelp,
她葬礼的地方离著名的
she's dead about two blocks
费城牛肉干酪三明治店只有两个街区
from the famous Philly cheese steak place.
- Max 体面点  -  我又不认识她
- Max, show some respect. - Well, I didn't know her.
其实 我就知道
In fact, I only know her as the
她就是让我有机会吃到牛肉干酪三明治的女士
lady who brought me and cheese steaks together.
即便我们从未谋面
Even though we've never met, it'll mean so much
Antonia的家人看到我能去致哀 他们会感到有意义的
to Antonia's Family that I came out of respect.
对我的心理医生来说
It'll mean so much to my therapist
我能只带着一只狗狗就脱离心理安全区 这也很有意义
that I left my safe zone and only brought one of the dogs.
Max 你觉得我在悼词里加上
Max, do you think in addition to my eulogy,
一些我小时候的日记如何
I should read something from my childhood journal?
我不建议 但你还是会一意孤行的
I don't, but I think you're gonna do it anyway.
"1997年的圣诞节清晨"
"Christmas morning, 1997.
"Antonia用一杯热可可"
"Antonia woke me up with a cup of hot cocoa"
"还有我最爱吃的薄荷棒糖叫醒我 然后我们就去打开礼物"
"And my favorite peppermint stick, and then we opened presents."
1997年的圣诞节清晨
Christmas morning, 1997.
我泼了我妈妈一脸的冷水
I threw cold water on my mother's face.
到了新年那天 她纹风不动
New Year's day... Still no movement.
这张照片是我留下来唯一一张和她的合影
This is the only picture I still have of us.
第一个一起过的万圣节 那时我才四岁
It was our first Halloween together. I was four.
看看这是她给我做的小鸡服装
Look at that cute little baby chick costume she made me.
- 哇 真可爱  - 看着点路
- Aw, so cute. - Car.
我从来就没穿过万圣节服装
I never had a Halloween costume.
我曾经梳着凌乱发髻
I used to put my hair in a messy bun
然后走路蹒跚挨家挨户的敲门假扮我妈
and stumble from door-to-door telling people I was my mother.
这个万圣节 我打扮我的医生Michael
This Halloween, I went as my doctor, Michael.
我把这小狗狗打扮成他的恋人Joseph
And I dressed up my buddy here as his lover, Joseph.
我们一时情迷意乱了
We lost.
Antonia一直守护着我
Antonia was always there for me...
万圣节 圣诞节 复活节 每个节日都在我身边
Halloween, Christmas, Easter... Every holiday.
每一天
Really, every day.
她就像我的妈妈
She was really like a mother to me.
那你亲妈去哪儿了
Where was your real mother?
哟 你这狗除了有着悲伤基因以外算什么品种
Hey, what kind of dog is that? I mean, besides "Sad"?
她娘红杏出墙 被她爹休了
Her mother had an affair, got pushed out.
这是她的伤心往事 你别再提了
That's her hot spot, so don't lick it.
没事的 Max 我已经不需要保护了
It's okay, Max, I don't need any protection.
你不需要保护
You don't need protection?
你以为你是我前男友们啊
Who are you, every guy I've ever dated?
Bebe 是的 我妈妈对我爸爸不忠 然后被赶出了家门
Bebe, yes, my mother was unfaithful to my father, so she was sent away.
但是我身边还有Antonia 她一直在照顾我
But I had Antonia and she took care of me.
她就是我的家人
She was my family.
你人生太苦逼了 每个人都需要个妈
That must have been hard. Everybody needs a mother.
如果我妈不在的话我得疯了
I'd be crazy without my mother.
每次她都会开车戴我去看医生
She drives me to all my appointments.
但现在你在开车
But you drive.
是啊
Yeah...
但是我不该开的
But I'm not supposed to.
我让Bebe在车里等没什么问题吧
It's okay I asked Bebe to wait in the car, right?
她会好好的对吧 我们还给她开了扇车窗
I mean, she'll be okay. We cracked a window.
恩 她有个碗及咀嚼玩具
Yeah, and she's got a bowl and a chew-toy.
快 我们来登记
Come on, let's sign in.
Max 当我见到她家人的时候 我得振作起来
Max, I have to keep it together when I meet the family.
我不能太情绪化
I can't be all emotional.
看 我手还在抖 真可怕
Look, my hand's shaking. This is terrible.
怎么了 我签的不好嘛
What? It was a terrible signature.
而且这张纸上只有五个名字而已
And there were only five other names on the page.
把它处理掉
Get rid of it.
"Get rid of it"?
你以为你是我前男友们啊
Who are you, every guy I've ever dated?
Caroline Channing
"Caroline Channing."
给你 Max
Here, Max.
喔 看
Oh, look.
这鲜花还有这里的一切是多么美
The flowers and everything are so beautiful.
写好了
There you go.
你竟然签了"费城.牛肉干酪三明治"
You signed "Phil E. Cheese Steak"?
你跟我说别老提着 所以我就写下来当个提醒
You told me not to mention it anymore, so it's just a reminder.
好吧 Max 这里会有许多想跟我攀谈的人
Okay, Max, there are gonna be a lot of people
所以你要耐心一点
who will want my attention, so please be patient
站在我旁边 偶尔给点精神上的依靠
and stand next to me for the occasional supportive lean.
如果有人开始涕泗横流
And if someone starts to get too weepy,
你赶紧把他们拉开 因为我这件儿衣服可不能沾上眼泪
push them out of the way because I can't get tears on this dress.
我得明天早上9点前把它还回Barneys
It has to be back to Barneys by 9:00 A.M.
- 你来了  - 做好准备 Max
- You're here. - Here we go, Max.
其实我在跟他说话
I was talking to him.
那必须 真是个悲伤的日子
Of course you were. It's a very sad day for us all.
那真是乱来
That was rough.
喔 Max 看 这是Antonia
Oh. Max, look. This is Antonia.
- 哇 她看起来很和蔼可亲  - 是的
- Wow. She looks really nice. - She was.
我不知道她曾经参加过军队
I didn't know she was in the military.
这倒能够解释那些整齐床单的由来
But it does explain those fabulous bed sheet corners.
等一下 你不知道你保姆曾经是个陆战队
Wait, you didn't know your nanny was a marine?
真不幸 如果我知道我就会说
That's too bad, 'cause I'd be all,
"哟 有钱的小不点们 老子的保姆能折断你们的脖子"
"Yo, other little rich kid! My nanny can snap your neck."
喔 看 这是她的妹妹 Cecelia和Angela
Oh, look. There are her sisters, Cecelia and Angela,
还有她可爱的侄子和侄女
and there are her nieces and nephews.
但是竟然没有我
And there is not me anywhere.
我的照片一定是和其他的VIP照片一起放在棺材里
You know, my picture must be in the coffin with the other V.I.P.S.
如果你是VIP的话 能给我们拿瓶酒吗
If you're a V.I.P., can we get some bottle service?
女士们下午好 我是Anthony Antonia的侄子
Good afternoon, ladies. I'm Anthony, Antonia's Nephew.
- 真是太悲伤了 不是吗  - 是的
- It's sad day, huh? - Yes, it is.
- 我想我能得到些许安慰了  - 拿开你的咸猪手 Anthony
- Think I just got a little less sad. - Oh! Anthony!
快停下 我们是一家人 我是Caroline Channing
Stop. We're family. I'm Caroline Channing.
我只知道你是 性感Caroline
You're Caroline "Hot," Is all I know.
你们需要信封装钱吗 还是你们无所谓
You ladies need cash envelopes or you guys cool?
我总是需要装满现金的信封
I always need a cash envelope.
不好意思 为什么需要信封
I'm sorry, envelopes for what?
在意大利文化中守丧时 哀悼者需要
Well, at Italian wakes, the mourners give the family
在拜谒过亡者之后给家属一定的捐款
a donation after they view the deceased.
按次计费
So it's pay-per-view?
哇 你戳中了我的笑点
That was a good one.
嗨 你们一会儿想一块喝杯嘛
Hey, you want to go get a pop later?
我们一会儿就走 但是Anthony
We're leaving right after, but yes, Anthony.
我们需要个信封
Thank you. We'll take an envelope.
好吧 走过去就能看到她了
All right.The body's right through there.
- 向前走  - Anthony 住手
- Go right ahead. - Anthony, stop.
我很紧张 以前还从没见过死人
I'm really nervous. I've never seen a dead body before.
我见过一堆 我还跟几个之死有关
I've seen a bunch. A couple of them were my fault.
我没有现金 你有吗
I don't have any cash. Do you have any money?
我来看看
Let me check my wallet.
这可是真正的密封塑料袋 可不是山寨货
This is a real Ziploc, not one of those knock-offs.
把信封封好
Make sure you seal the envelope,
大家就都会以为里边装的都是25美分硬币
so people think it's all quarters.
Max 马上就到我们了 我有点害怕 牵着我的手
Max, we're next. I'm afraid. Hold my hand.
牵你的手 我们是约会网里第五次约会的情侣吗
Hold hands? What are we? On a Christian mingle fifth date?
拜托了 Max我有点紧张
Please, Max. I'm nervous.
- 喔 老天  - 谢谢你
- Oh, God. - Thank you.
好 放手
Okay. Now give it back.
怎么了 那已经是我最长的关系了
What? That was just my longest relationship.
另外 我需要我的手来把硬币装进信封
Plus, I need it to put this change in the envelope.
喔 她看起来是多么慈祥
Oh, she looks so peaceful.
嗨 Antonia 我是Caroline
Hi, Antonia. It's me, Caroline.
我要亲亲她吗 这个家的人都在看着呢
Should I kiss her? The family is right there watching.
在我们之前的女士亲了她
The lady before us kissed her.
上吧 她看起来不会打你
Go for it. Doesn't look like she'd fight you.
好的 从一数到三
Okay, on the count of three.
一 二
One, two...
Max 快来牵着我的手 我要
No! Max, hold my hand again while I...
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
手拿开 这些无论如何都得留下
Wait, leave it! We were giving it to them anyway.
也别全留下啊 这些是我们买牛肉干酪三明治的钱
Not all of it. That's our cheese steak money.
留下 走吧
Leave it. Come on.
真的很不好意思
I am so, so sorry about that.
我太紧张了 希望你理解
My nerves got the best of me. You understand.
- 我是Cecelia Antonia  - 的妹妹 我知道
- I'm Cecelia, Antonia??... - Sister. I know.
你们俩长得很像 我是Caroline
I see the resemblance. I'm Caroline.
姓什么
Caroline who?
Caroline Channing
Oh. Caroline Channing.
Caroline Channing是谁
Caroline Channing who?
我很理解 你现在在度过一个很困难的时刻
You're having a hard time processing. Understandable.
今天真的带给我们很大的冲击
It's been a very emotional day for us all.
这个女孩是谁 你 我觉得我好像在哪见过你
Who is this girl? You, I feel like I've seen somewhere.
你是Ricky那住在罗彻斯特的女人吗
Are you Ricky's girl from Rochester?
也许是 怎么了
I could be. What's in it for me?
Antonia在我小时候一直照顾我
Antonia used to take care of me when I was little.
哦 Antonia是你的临时保姆
Oh, Antonia was your baby-sitter.
很感谢你的到来
Very nice of you to come.
她不止是我的临时保姆
Well, she was hardly my "Baby-sitter."
十年来的日日夜夜都是她在照顾着我
She took care of me every day for ten years.
Caroline Caroline Channing
Caroline. Caroline Channing.
不好意思 宝贝 我真的不认识你
I'm sorry, but I don't know who you are, sweetheart,
即使你一再强调地提示我
though it seems to be what you're hammering me about.
不好意思 我想抽根烟
If you'll excuse me, I need a cigarette.
我还得把那些硬币从我姐姐身上拿开
And then I got to remove some of those pennies off of my sister.
这个是棺材 不是许愿池
It's a coffin, not a wishing well.
这个葬礼变得好沉重
This funeral turned out to be very depressing.
是啊
Well, yeah.
房间里的死人 真扫兴
Dead body in the room, generally a buzz-kill.
除非是一个爱尔兰式的葬礼
Unless it's an Irish wake...
你就可以在棺材旁边玩啤酒桌球赛了
Then you're playing beer pong off the coffin.
不 我是说 为什么这个家的人居然会不认识我
No, I mean, how is it possible that the family doesn't know me?
难道Antonia没跟她们提过我
Did Antonia never even mention me?
我们往好的方面想 Antonia很喜欢你的翘臀
Let's focus on the positive. Anthony really liked your ass.
我就知道Antonia和我拥有的是什么了
I know what Antonia and I had.
就是这
This is what we had.
啾啾 这就是我们拥有的
Peep, peep. That's what we had.
好吧 还真多
Well, that's a lot.
但是我觉得这家人
But I guess no one in this family
没人想承认这个事情 真遗憾
wants to admit that, and it's a shame too,
我的悼词很美
because I had a great eulogy.
真的吗
You do?
那当然 你想听听吗
Yes. I do. Would you like me to share it with you?
乐意之极
I most certainly would.
你不是真的要给那位老女人念悼词吧
You are not seriously eulogy-bombing that old lady, are you?
她主动问我的悼词
She asked me about my great eulogy.
她都能有100岁了 她极有可能
She's a hundred. She probably
以为你说你有一个很棒的泌尿科医生
thought you said you had a great urologist.
有笔没 我要记一下医生的名字
Do you have a pen? I'm getting the name of her doctor.
不 我没有说
No, ma'am, I didn't say,
泌尿科医生 我说的是 悼词 非常完美的悼词
"Urologist." I said, "Eulogy." A great eulogy.
为什么要写悼词
Why would you give the eulogy?
因为我是 Caroline Channing
Because I'm Caroline Channing.
- 谁  - Caroline Channing
- Who? - Caroline Channing.
我是Caroline Channing Antonia是我的保姆
Caroline Channing...? Antonia was my nanny.
我曾经非常富有
My family was rich,
但是 我父亲骗了大家的钱
but then my father robbed everyone,
我们变成了过街老鼠
and we became the scourge of society,
Mel Gibson在同一周发表了反犹太人宣言
overshadowed a little bit
所以他的风头稍微盖过了我们一点点
by Mel Gibson hating the Jews that same week.
这下你想起来了吗
Surely, you remember?
宝贝 我甚至都不记得我是怎么到这儿的
Honey, I don't even remember how I got here.
我不相信
I can't believe this.
我努力为自己创造一个幸福的童年的故事
I constructed my entire "Happy" Childhood
尽管事实上
on the fact that even though
我母亲离开了我 而且她根本不爱我
my mom left and apparently didn't love me,
但我认为Antonia是爱我的
Antonia did.
可我来到了这儿
And now I get here and I
然后忽然意识到 根本没有人爱我
我在她眼中只是张付薪水支票
realize no one loved me, I was just a paycheck.
我就是她众多照料的孩子中的一个而已
One of the many kids she baby-sat.
我都不知道我为什么要来
I don't even know why I bothered to come.
我要去卫生间呆会儿 然后我们就走吧
I'm gonna go to the restroom and then we can just leave.
不好意思 嗨
Excuse me. Hi.
我是Max Ricky的女人
Max, Ricky's girl.
我知道这段时间对你来说很痛苦
I know this is a hard time for you,
但是对我的朋友来说也一样
but it's a hard time for my friend as well.
尽管 可能你从来都没听说过她
And even though you never heard of her,
但你可不可以走过去
I was wondering if you could just go over there,
然后告诉她 你刚刚记起她了
and say you just remembered her,
其实Antonia一直都有和你们提到过她
and that Antonia talked about her all the time?
我知道你得推翻说过的话 而且还是个谎言
I know it's a 180 on your original story and a lie,
我愿意付钱解忧
and I'd offer to pay you for your trouble,
但是我的退休金都掉进那个棺材里 你姐姐身上了
but my 401k is laying in that box on top of your sister.
听着 我之所以让你们两个呆在这里
Look, I only permitted you two to stay
完全是因为Joe叔叔去年从房顶上掉下来之后
'cause your Ricky was so nice to Uncle Joe
Ricky对他一直都很好
when he fell off the roof last year.
但是现在 你赶紧滚
But now, you gotta go.
好吧 没问题
Okay. Be that way.
但是不要指望Ricky会带Joe叔叔去做透析
But don't expect Ricky to pick up Uncle Joe for dialysis.
Max 你干嘛呢
Max, what are you doing?
那家人让我把照片放上 他们刚刚想起来你了
The family asked me to put it up. They just remembered you.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我太可悲了
I'm so pathetic, you have
你为了让我感觉好过一点 而把我的照片放上去
to put up my picture to make me feel better?
从某种角度来说 是的
In a way, yes.
它就是属于这里的 怎么会有人不想认识这个孩子呢
It belongs up there. Who wouldn't want to know that kid?
很高兴认识你 Antonia 但是就请不要来我们家串门了
Nice to meet you, Antonia. Please don't haunt us.
现在 我们该出发了 去吃一些好吃到爆的牛肉干酪三明治
Now, let's hit the road and get some freaking cheese steaks!
Max 把那个拿下来吧 太让人难为情了
Max, please take that down. It's so embarrassing.
在这儿 没有人认识我
Nobody here knows anything about me.
他们也不认识我 小鸡仔
They didn't know me either, chicken.
嘿 你叫谁小鸡仔呢
Hey, who you callin' chicken?
是我 那是Antonia给我起的昵称
Me. That was Antonia's Nickname for me.
- 你知道我是谁  - 当然
- You know who I am? - Of course I do.
Antonia的小鸡仔 唧唧叫的小鸡仔
Antonia's little chick, her peep.
她是爱你的
She loved you.
她做那套服装时也很高兴
And she loved making you that costume.
把整个厨房餐桌都弄得都是闪片
Took the whole kitchen table up with all those sequins,
她知道你值得光耀照人
but she knew you deserved to sparkle.
她非常非常爱你 让我都没法抱怨
She loved you so much, I couldn't begin to complain.
很抱歉 你叫什么
I'm so sorry. What was your name?
Meg O'Hara 我是她的室友
I'm Meg O'Hara. I was her roommate.
和爱人
And lover.
我们在一起30年了
We were together 30 years.
陆战队那张照片中的人是你
The military!
我晓 这不明显吗
I know, right? I mean, come on.
在坦克前面 我的手环抱着她的肩膀
That's me with my arm around her on that tank.
可是她家族里的人还傻傻的不知道
And the family still had no clue.
拉拉历史的先驱 太酷了
Vintage lez... Very cool.
我知道 Toni一定想让你保留这些东西
I know Toni would have wanted you to have these.
感谢你能来 小鸡仔
Oh, thanks for coming, chicken.
你可能是这个世界上唯一一个
You're probably the only person in the world
和我一样 全身心爱着她的人
who loved her as purely as I did.
Max 看哪
Max, look.
圣诞节
Christmas.
我的生日
And my birthday.
美国青少年选择奖
And the Teen Choice Awards.
节哀顺变
I'm sorry for your loss.
谢谢
Thank you.
大家一起来享用费城牛肉干酪三明治吧
Philly cheese steaks for everybody!
和9件牛肉干酪三明治以及一只
And you really haven't lived
会放屁的狗狗一起待在雪佛兰里
until you've driven two hours in a Chevy
两个小时过后 这才算是活了过来
with nine cheese steaks and a gassy animal.
怎么了 我的都在车上吃完了
What? I ate mine in the car.
嗨 Earl 你错过了
Hey, Earl, you missed one
一个超级酷的葬礼 你应该来的
hell of a funeral. You should have come.
有一些炫酷的老人
There were some hot octogenarians,
他们中都有人想约我了
and I got a definite "Jungle fever" Vibe from one of them.
姑娘们 在我的年纪 你不会想去任何和葬礼有关的地方
Girl, at my age, you don't go anywhere near funerals.
一旦你不小心睡着了 你就要花六个小时
You accidentally doze off, you spend six hours
把自己从地里挖上来
digging yourself out of the ground.
嗨 小鸡仔 你怎么样
Hey, how you holding up, chicken?
我很好 谢谢
I'm okay. Thanks.
Max 等我死了的时候
And Max, when I die,
我才不会在乎谁来我的葬礼
I don't care who else is at my funeral,
只要你在就好
as long as you're there.
我当然会在那儿
Of course I'll be there.
为了避嫌 杀人犯总会在葬礼上出现的
The murderer always shows up to throw off the cops.
还有 不用买棺材了
Also, save the money on a casket
就让我穿着Dior 画着烟熏装 随便扔个洞里就行
and just toss me in a hole wearing Dior and a smoky eye.
除非 我变胖了 就把我火化了吧
Unless I'm fat... Then burn me.
好吧 我不想要什么葬礼
Well, I don't want a funeral.
等我死了 就把我的尸体塞进大炮里吧
When I die, just shove my corpse into a Cannon
直接对准特朗普赌场就行
and blow me directly into the Trump Casino.
目前总资产：77刀
== 破产姐妹 第三季 第11集 完【H-SGDK】字幕组倾情奉献 ==
== 【H-SGDK】字幕组欢迎各位加入
有意者请加QQ群109164858，注明 字幕组+申请职位即可 ==
胸大梗 Max自夸胸大如婴儿 让警察看错
Gordon Ramsay 地狱厨房主持 狂人一名
体位梗
Nelly Furtado 葡萄牙裔的加拿大女歌手 歌曲创作者 演员
Chipotle墨西哥餐厅
Wrecking ball这玩意别说你不懂
真不懂请去看MV
white dwarfs = 小型(矮梗) black holes = 洞梗
Uranus = 一个小学级的烂屁股笑话
又是体位梗 双关Han永远是被骑的
热点病 急性湿性皮肤炎 通常好发于毛层致密的犬种
跟归西的待了起码一周 Max你强大……
不戴套梗
这回是堕胎梗了
Barneys 美国高级时装店
整瓶服务/bottle service 这是高档酒吧或夜总会的一个特色服务
Christian mingle 基督徒在线约会网站
Peep peep 是小鸡的叫声 对应先前那小鸡服装
eulogy与urologist音近
401k 是美国于1981年创立一种延后课税的退休金帐户计划
Jungle fever俚语指非黑人约会黑人